offliberty.co 2018-10-04

# Offliberty - for offline people

Offliberty - for offline people

**Privacy Policy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

Please read the following carefully. If you have any questions or concerns, please send us an email at [contact@offliberty.com](mailto:contact@offliberty.com).

**Gathering and Use of Information**

Offliberty will never willfully disclose any personally identifiable information about our online audience to any third party without first receiving the user's permission. We do not collect personally identifiable information from our visitors other than what is supplied to us on a voluntary basis.

Visitors to the Offliberty Web Site may voluntarily supply certain personally identifiable information in connection with (i)contest or sweepstakes registration, (ii) subscription registration for sites or services which require subscription (such as email newsletters), (iii) requests for membership information and (iv) e-commerce transactions. In addition, personally identifiable information is voluntarily provided in connection with certain content submissions, community postings (i.e., forums or bulletin boards), comments and suggestions, or voting.

Some of our sites contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

Offliberty may use such information only for conducting the activities stated above, for internal marketing and promotional purposes, or, on occasion, when mailing lists are made available to other organizations. (The occasional provision of mailing lists to such organizations is the only case where such information would be provided to third parties).

If the visitor does not want this information collected and used by us for the disclosed internal purposes, the visitor is given an opportunity to 'opt-out.' Our visitors need to recognize, however, that under certain circumstances, if they select to 'opt-out' they may not be eligible for certain activities for which the personally identifiable information is needed. (For example, if a contest participant elects to 'opt-out' on permitting us to collect and use their personal information, we cannot contact them if they win without using such information.)

**Cookies**

We use a number of different cookies on our site. If you do not know what cookies are, or how to control or delete them, then we recommend you visit http://www.aboutcookies.org for detailed guidance. 

Below we describe the cookies we use on this site and what we use them for. Currently we operate an ‘implied consent’ policy which means that we assume you are happy with this usage. If you are not happy, then you should either not use this site, or you should delete Offliberty cookies having visited the site, or you should browse the site using your browser’s anonymous usage setting (called “Incognito” in Chrome, “InPrivate” for Internet Explorer, "Private Browsing" in Firefox and Safari etc.) 

**"Session" Cookies**

We use a session cookie to remember your activity. These we deem strictly necessary to the working of the website. If these are disabled then various functionality on the site will be broken. More information on session cookies and what they are used for at http://www.allaboutcookies.org/cookies/session-cookies-used-for.html 

**Persistent Cookies for Site Analytics and Performance**

We use some persistent cookies to enhance the relevancy of information displayed on the site. User data is anonymous. More information about persistent cookies and what they are used for at http://www.allaboutcookies.org/cookies/persistent-cookies-used-for.html 

**Google AdSense** – this cookie is used by Google to report to us how the adverts shown on Offliberty.com are performing. User data is all anonymous. You can find out more generally about Google and its policies and principles as regards advertising at http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/ 

**DoubleClick (Google)** – this is very similar to the cookie above (both are owned/controlled by Google) but is specific to the display advertising on Offliberty’s site. User data is anonymous. As above, you can find out more generally about Google and its policies and principles as regards advertising at http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/ 

**Google Analytics** – we use this to understand how the site is being used in order to improve the user experience. User data is all anonymous. You can find out more about Google’s position on privacy as regards its analytics service at http://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html 

**Social buttons.** On many of the pages of the site you will see ‘social buttons’. These enable users to share or bookmark the web pages. There are buttons for: Twitter, Google +1, Facebook ‘Like’. In order to implement these buttons, and connect them to the relevant social networks and external sites, there are scripts from domains outside of Offliberty. You should be aware that these sites are likely to be collecting information about what you are doing all around the internet, including on Offliberty’s site. So if you click on any of these buttons, these sites will be registering that action and may use that information. In some cases these sites will be registering the fact that you are visiting Offliberty, and the specific pages you are on, even if you don’t click on the button if you are logged into their services, like Google and Facebook. You should check the respective policies of each of these sites to see how exactly they use your information and to find out how to opt out, or delete, such information. 

**Email tracking.** Emails we send we put in tracking so that we can tell how much traffic those emails send to our site but we do not know who has clicked so the data is anonymous e.g. our daily newsletter. Some emails we can track, at an individual level, whether the user has opened and clicked on the email. We rarely use the latter information at a personal level, rather we use it to understand open and click rates on our emails to try and improve them. Sometimes we do use the personal information e.g. to re-email people who didn’t click the first time. If you want to be sure that none of your email activity is tracked then you should opt out of Offliberty’s emails. 

**Acceptance of these Offliberty Web Site Privacy Policy Terms and Conditions**

By using this site, you signify your agreement to the terms and conditions of this Offliberty Web Site Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, please do not use the site. We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time.

From time to time, Offliberty may update this privacy notice. We will notify you about material changes in the way we treat personally identifiable information by placing a notice on our site. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it. Your continued use of the Offliberty Web Site following the posting of any changes to these terms shall mean that you have accepted those changes.

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please email us at [contact@offliberty.com](mailto:contact@offliberty.com).
